en:
  questions:
    captions:
      points: 'points'
      views: 'views'
      answers: 'answers'
      upvotes: 'upvotes'
      downvotes: 'downvotes'
      tagged_questions: 'Tagged Questions'
      no_questions_bookmarked: 'No Questions are Bookmarked'
      teacher_asks_no_questions: 'has not asked any Question'
      no_questions_asked_by_user: 'You have not asked any Question'
      no_questions_tagged: 'has not tagged any Question'
      no_questions_tagged_by_you: 'You have not tagged any Question'
    messages:
      question_not_found: 'No such Question found for Delete!'
      delete_success: 'Deleted Successfuly!'
      profile_update: 'Profile updated'
      block_list_empty: 'No Questions are Blocked'
      create: 'Please fill proper values'
    table:
      header:
        title: 'Question Title'
        action: 'Action'
    page_header:
      title: 'Question'
      title_for_new: 'New Question'
    basic:
      answer_by: 'Answered by'
      asked_by: 'Asked By'
      tag_on_index: 'Tags:'
      view: 'Views:'
      answers: 'Answers'
      tag_on_new: "Tags (separated by commas)"
      content_label: 'Content:'
      answered: 'Answered'
    btn:
      new_question: 'New Question'
      submit: 'Submit'
    links:
      add_bookmark: 'Add to Bookmark'
      delete_bookmark: 'Remove from Bookmark'
      report_abuse: 'Report Abuse'
      all: 'All'
      newest: 'Newest'
      last_week: 'Last Week'
      last_month: 'Last Month'
      most_viewed: 'Most Viewed'
      most_voted: 'Most Voted '
      unanswered: 'Unanswered'
    error:
      message: 'No Questions Available'
  answers:
    messages:
      contains_error: 'Must contain some text'
      answer_not_found: 'No such Answer found!'
      update_success: 'Updated Successfully!'
      delete_success: 'Deleted successfully!'
      answer_accepted: 'Answer Accepted!'
      unauthorized: 'You are not authorized for this action'
    basic:
      answer_label: 'Your answer'
      new_answer: 'New Answer'
      teacher_not_answered: 'has not answered any Question'
      user_not_answered: 'You have not answered any Question'

    btn:
      submit_answer: 'Submit'
    links:
      make_right: 'Make Right'
      correct_answer: 'Correct Answer'
      delete: '| Delete'
      edit: '| Edit'
      add_comment: 'Add Comment'
  comments:
    captions:
      edit_comment_of_question: 'Edit Comment of Question'
    messages:
      update_success: 'Updated Successfully'
      comment_not_found: 'No such Comment found'
      successful_delete: 'Deleted Successfully!'
      create: 'Please insert Proper value'
    commentable:
      teacher: 'Teacher'
  tags:
    header:
      title: 'Tags'
    message:
      create_success: 'Tag created Successfully'
      create_failure: 'Cannot create tag. Something went wrong.'
      update_success: 'Tag updated Successfully'
      destroy_success: 'Tag destroyed successfully'
      destroy_failure: 'Tag destruction failed'
  badges:
    captions:
      points_require: 'points require'
      with_you_can: 'With you can do'
      edit_other_people: "Edit other people's questions"
      vote_to_close: 'Vote to close, reopen, or migrate questions'
      edit_others_answer: "Edit other people's answers"
      vote_down: 'Vote down (costs 1 point on answers)'
      leave_comment: 'Leave comments'
      vote_up: 'Vote up'
      point_system: 'Points System'
      earn_reputaion: 'You earn reputation when people vote on your posts'
      create_a_question: 'create a question'
      question_vote_up: 'question is voted up'
      answer_vote_up: 'answer is voted up'
      answer_accepted: 'answer is Accepted'
      badge_system: 'Badges System'
      add_badge: 'Add Badge'
      add_new_badge: 'Add New Badge'
      edit_badge: 'Edit Badge'
    message:
      badge_create_success: 'Badge Created'
      badge_create_fail: 'Badge Not Created'
      badge_update_success: 'Badge updated'
      badge_destroy_success: 'Badge destroy'
      badge_destroy_fail: 'Badge not destroy'
      not_earned_any_badge: 'has not earned any Badge'
      you_not_earned_any_badge: 'You have not earned any Badge'
  points:
    message:
      update_success: 'Points Updated '
      update_failed: 'Points not Updated'
  common:
    error:
      messages: 'No Record Found'
    messages:
      sign_in: 'Sign in First'
      create_bookmark: 'You have bookmark this question'
      delete_bookmark: 'Successfully delete bookmark'
      confirm_message: 'Are you sure?'
      unauthorized: 'You are not authorized for this action'
    captions:
      dob: 'Birthdate'
      first_name: 'First Name'
      middle_name: 'Middle Name'
      last_name: 'Last Name'
      user_name: 'User Name'
      email: 'Email'
      qualification: 'Qualification'
      password: 'Password'
      new_password: 'New Password'
      password_confirmation: 'Retype Password'
      current: 'Current Password'
      remember: 'Remember me'
      salutations: 'Salutations'
      set_avatar: 'Photo'
    btn:
      update: 'Update'
      ask_question: 'Ask Question'
      sign_in: 'Sign in'
      submit: 'Submit'
      post: 'Post'
    links:
      sign_in: 'Sign in'
      sign_up: 'Sign up'
      edit_your_info: 'Edit your Info'
      basic_info: 'Basic Info'
      question: 'Questions'
      badges: 'Badges'
      votes: 'Votes'
      forgot_password: 'Forgot your password?'
      last_week: 'Last week'
      last_month: 'Last Month'
      questions: 'Questions'
      answers: 'Answers'
      add_tag: ' Add Tag'
      bookmarks: 'Bookmarks'
      comment: 'Comment'
      disable: 'Disable'
      enable: 'Enable'
      edit: 'Edit'
      up_votes: 'Up Votes'
      down_votes: 'Down Votes'
      delete_link: 'Delete'
      delete:
        confirm: 'Are you sure?'
    image:
      alt: 'Image'
    active_tab:
      blocked_student: 'Blocked Students'
      student_for_review: 'Students for Review'
      students: 'Students'
      teachers: 'Teachers'
      managers: 'Managers'
      all: 'all'
      week: 'week'
      month: 'month'
      un_answered: 'un_answered'
      most_viewed: 'most_viewed'
      most_voted: 'most_voted'
      newest: 'newest'
      class_activeness: 'Class Activeness'
      used_tags: 'Used Tags'
      weakness: 'Weakness'
      strength: 'Strength'
      top_3_weak_area: 'Top 3 Weak Area'
      top_3_strong_area: 'Top 3 Strong Area'
    page_header:
      users: 'Users'
  students:
    captions:
      middle_name: 'Middle Name'
      class: 'Class'
      division: 'Division'
    page_header:
      title_confirmation: 'Resend confirmation instructions'
    basic:
      forgot_password: 'Forgot your password?'
    messages:
      blocked_profile: 'Your account has been blocked. Please contact to administrator'
    links:
      block : 'Block'
      mark_as_review: 'Mark as Review'
      review: 'Review'
      unblock: 'Unblock'
      unmark_review: 'Unmark Review'
      reports: 'Reports'
    tooltip:
      manager: 'Student Manager'
    filter:
      basic_info: 'basicinfo'
      questions: 'questions'
      answers: 'answers'
      tags: 'tags'
      badges: 'badges'
      votes: 'votes'
    active_tab:
      basic_info: 'basicinfo'
      questions: 'questions'
      answers: 'answers'
      tags: 'tags'
      badges: 'badges'
      votes: 'votes'
      bookmarks: 'bookmarks'
      edit_profile: 'edit-profile'
      reports: 'Reports'
  teachers:
    captions:
    page_header:
      title_confirmation: 'Resend confirmation instructions'
      title_sign_in: 'Sign in'
    basic:
      salutation: 'Salutations'
      title_sign_in: 'Sign in'
      student_manager: 'Student Manager'
      prompt: '----- Select Class -----'
  mailer:
    subject:
      report_abuse_notification: 'Report Abuse Notification'
  flash_message:
    error:
      teacher:
      student:
        manager: 'Already two Student manager selected.'
      question:
        edit: 'No such Question found for Edit!'
        update: 'No such Question found for Update!'
        destroy: 'No such Question found for Delete!'
        vote: 'No such Question found for Vote, Please refresh this page'
        show: 'The question you are searching for is not found!'
        disable: 'No such Question found for Disable!'
        report_abuse: 'No such Question found for Report!'
      answer:
        edit: 'No such Answer found for edit!'
        update: 'No such Answer found for Update!'
        destroy: 'No such Answer found for delete!'
        comment: 'no such Answer found for Comment!'
        vote: 'No such answer found for vote!'
        accept: 'No such answer found for accept!'
      comment:
        edit: 'No such comment found for edit!'
        update: 'No such comment found for update!'
        destroy:
      report:
        no_record: 'No Record Found'
        no_student: 'No Student Found'
        no_standard: 'No Standard Found'
    success:
      question:
        update: 'Question successfully updated!'
        destroy: 'Question successfuly deleted!'
        comment:
        report_abuse: 'report abuse mail successfully sent!'
      answer:
        update: 'Answer Successfully Updated.'
        destroy: 'Answer successfully Deleted.'
        comment:
        accept: 'Answer Accepted!'
      comment:
        edit:
        update: 'Comment Successfully Updated!'
        destroy:
  header_navigation:
    home: 'Home'
    users: 'Users'
    questions: 'Questions'
    tags: 'Tags'
    badges: 'Badges'
    edit_profile: 'Edit Profile'
    logout: 'Logout'
    profile: 'Profile'
    report: 'Report'
    badges: 'Badges'
    disabled_questions: 'Disabled Questions'
  right_side_bar:
    questions: 'Questions'
    students: 'Students'
    teachers: 'Teachers'
    most_used_tags: 'MOST USED TAGS'
    popular_question: 'Most Popular'
    see_more_tags: 'See more tags'
  administrators:
    btn:
      sign_in: 'Administrator'
  member:
    captions:
      not_answered: You don't  have answered any question yet
      never_ask: You don't have asked any questions yet
  administrator:
    cancel_account: 'Cancel my account'
    active_link:
      disabled_question: 'disabled_question'
      home: 'home'
  report:
    captions:
      select_artist: 'Select an Artist'
      top_3_weak_area: 'Top 3 weak Areas'
      top_3_strong_area: 'Top 3 strong Areas'
    page_headers:
      reports: 'Reports'

